https://www.needlepointnow.com/privacy-policy/

Tours
A Tale Of Two Cities Needlepoint Tour of London & Paris – Moved to April 2021
Off The Beaten Path Needlepoint Tour of England & Scotland – Moved to April, 2021
EB Designs Privacy Policy
EB Designs DBA Needlepoint Now is a private company held in the United States. This privacy policy will explain how our company uses your personal data is collected and used when you interact with our website and services.
What we collect:
Name, Address, Phone Numbers, Email addresses, and billing information if paying via credit card.
How do we collect your data?
You provide this data directly when using our online ordering system to subscribe, renew, or order back issues of the magazine, as well as when submitting a change of address or paying an invoice.
We may also receive address information from NCOS or USPS for verifying addresses so that we can ship your magazines correctly.
How will we use your data?
EB Designs collects the minimum information necessary to process orders and deliver magazine subscriptions to our customers. This includes charging your order to your credit card or PayPal, and submitting your address to out mail house (Lynx Group, Salem, OR) for delivery purposes.
Except where noted above, EB Design does not share customer information with third parties.
How do we store your data?
EB Designs store minimum data on our servers in Oregon, USA. Payment information is not kept on file. Full account information and order history is kept to a minimum and stored on our internal systems not connected to our website. Information is stored indefinitely for auditing purposes.
Data Protection Rights.
In compliance with State, Federal, and International laws regarding customer Privacy, every user is entitled to the following:
The Right to Access – You have a right to request EB Designs for copies of your personal data. We may charge a small fee for this service
The Right to Rectification –You have the right to request that our company correct incorrect information or incomplete.
The Right to Erasure – You have the right, under certain conditions, to erase your personal data.
The Right to Restrict Processing –  You have the right to request EB Design restrict the processing of your personal data under certain circumstances.
Right to data portability – You have the right to have the information we collect transferred to yourself or another institution, under certain circumstances.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please email circulation@needlepointnow.com or by writing us at
Needlepoint Now
PO BOX 428
Elmira, OR 97437
Cookie Policy
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our website, we may collect certain information automatically  from you using cookies or similar technology
For more information on cookies, visit allaboutcookies.org
How we use cookies:
EB Designs uses cookies in a number of ways to improve your experience on our website, including managing logins, order processing, and displaying related products.
3rd Party cookies:
Third party cookies are limited to passing information back from our payment processor, as well as our security and auditing software that maintains the integrity of our site.
How to manage cookies:
You can set your browser to not accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies in most popular browsers. However, in some cases, some website features may not function as a result.
Scope of policy:
Needlepointnow.com contains links to third party resources, products, and advertisers. This policy only pertains to pages under the needlepointnow.com domain. If you follow links out to other sites, please consult their privacy and cookie policies.
Changes to our policy:
EB Designs keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates in this document. This privacy policy was last updated June 5th, 2019.
How to contact us:
Email: editor@needlepointnow.com
Phone: (541) 935-0238  Monday through Friday, 9-4 Pacific time
Writing:
Needlepoint Now
PO 428
Elmira, OR 97437
How to contact the appropriate authority:
Should you wish to report a complaint or feel that our company has not addressed your concern in a satisfactory manner, you may contact the authority appropriate to your jurisdiction.
About Us Published six times a year, every issue of Needlepoint Now includes intriguing needlepoint designs, innovative techniques, reviews on the latest accessories and books, and even a bit of humor. If you are a canvas work enthusiast, Needlepoint Now is the perfect magazine for you.
Follow Us On Social Media
—
—
Advertise With Us Needlepoint Now is the only commercial magazine dedicated solely to the art of needlepoint. With a readership of about 10,000 readers, when you advertise with us, you are placing your work and retail information in front of a large and passionate audience.
Learn More.
Quick MenuHome
Digital Back Issues
Click Here to Subscribe to Needlepoint Now
Current Issue
Back Issues
Tours
Newsletter
Where to Buy Needlepoint Now
Project Index
Advertising
Privacy Policy
Cart
Copyright © 2020 — Needlepoint Now. All Rights Reserved
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. Please see our Cookie and Privacy policy to see what data is used by our siteOkPrivacy policy
